https://transformationaltools.com/home/privacy-policy/

Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Transformational Tools, LLC . This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by our two websites: transformationaltools.com and thepowerofcolor.com. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through this website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
Transformational Tools LLC (dba The Power of Color) is the sole owner of the information collected on this website. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will never sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will never share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. We will call you only if we have a direct question about your order or information.
Your Access To and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone on our website given.
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via this website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the website page.  All credit card information is given through Paypal who has their own encryption.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Orders
We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (i.e. name, shipping address, phone number) and financial information collected by Paypal which we have not access to (i.e. credit card number, expiration date). If we have trouble processing an order, we will use the information provided by you to contact you.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (360)450-6849 or via our contact form.
Recent Posts
Are We There Yet?
Fruits of Love
Relationship Reset
Resilience through Emerald Green
Are You Experiencing Some of This Too?
Recent Commentstransformationaltools on Are We There Yet?Judith Cowan on Are We There Yet?transformationaltools on This is a time of Resurrection, so Why Am I Crying?Nancy on This is a time of Resurrection, so Why Am I Crying?transformationaltools on My Uncharacteristic Rant Archives
November 2020
July 2020
May 2020
April 2020
February 2020
November 2019
September 2019
August 2019
